<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on Expluce Player</title>
        <link>https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/page.html</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on Expluce Player</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/about.html</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/about.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome&#34;&gt;Welcome&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;strong&gt;Expluce Player&lt;/strong&gt;, the home of audiovisual content from the mind of me - Keoni D&amp;rsquo;Souza!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve contributed to an ever-increasing collection of radio shows, podcasts and have presented a handful of recorded productions. I am - slowly, but surely - updating this site so that people (mainly me&amp;hellip;) can enjoy my unimitable brand of top-quality low-quality content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Organised into overarching categories (audio and video) and series (for continuing content), each audio and video clip is accompanied by tags to help mark regular co-contributors and original broadcast partners (including Xtreme Radio, University Radio York and York Student Television).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, have a look around - you may find something that you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t even want to share with even your worst enemy&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keoni&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;expluce&#34;&gt;Expluce&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started branding everything I made since late 2010 with &lt;em&gt;KD Group&lt;/em&gt; to add my mark and help communicate that I was behind it. On 10th September 2013, the brand changed to &lt;em&gt;Expluce&lt;/em&gt; (originally with an exclamation mark), a portmanteau formed from the slogan, &lt;em&gt;Exploring excitement, inducing success&lt;/em&gt;. In 2017, &lt;strong&gt;Expluce Player&lt;/strong&gt; was launched with the aim to host my plethora of audio and video content all in one place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;collnod&#34;&gt;Collnod&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Collnod Ltd&lt;/em&gt; was formed on 28th December 2021 to facilitate employment contracts for freelance media opportunities. It is registered at 86-90 Paul Street, London, EC2A 4NE. Acting as a portfolio, since April, &lt;strong&gt;Expluce Player&lt;/strong&gt; has been funded and hosted by &lt;em&gt;Collnod Ltd&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Collnod&lt;/em&gt; is Welsh for &lt;em&gt;apostrophe&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/archives.html</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/archives.html</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/search.html</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beta.expluceplayer.co.uk/search.html</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
